Prusy B-Location
, I-Location
Opatów I-Location
County I-Location

Fluor B-Organization
Field I-Organization
at I-Organization
the I-Organization
West I-Organization
End I-Organization

Days B-Organization
of I-Organization
Our I-Organization
Lives I-Organization
'' O

' O
'' O
David B-Person
Beddall I-Person
'' O
' O

Mary B-Person
Hon I-Person
, O
Shek B-Person
Sau I-Person

Bassano B-Organization
– O
Bassano B-Location
del I-Location
Grappa I-Location

Louisville B-Location
, I-Location
Kentucky I-Location

Southern B-Location
Patagonian I-Location
Ice I-Location
Field I-Location

Uche B-Person
Okafor I-Person
( O
D O
) O

Piedmont B-Organization
Park I-Organization
• O
Atlanta B-Organization
, I-Organization
GA I-Organization

René B-Person
Cardona I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person

Anne-Catherine B-Person
de I-Person
Ligniville I-Person
, I-Person
Madame I-Person
Helvétius I-Person

Aga B-Organization
Khan I-Organization
Fund I-Organization
for I-Organization
Economic I-Organization
Development I-Organization

Andreiașu B-Location
de I-Location
Jos I-Location

Wundt B-Organization
, I-Organization
W I-Organization
. I-Organization
( O
1906 O
) O
. O

It O
was O
abolished O
on O
1 O
April O
1997 O
and O
replaced O
by O
Brighton B-Location
and I-Location
Hove I-Location
. O

Keiraville B-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
South I-Location
Wales I-Location

*Format O
: O
LP B-Organization
, O
CD B-Organization

New B-Organization
Forest I-Organization
Wildlife I-Organization
Park I-Organization
- O
Hampshire B-Location

Ridgeville B-Location
Township I-Location
, I-Location
Lorain I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location
( O
defunct O
) O

Minister B-Location
of I-Location
Arts I-Location
and I-Location
Culture I-Location

'' O
Khmer B-Location
Empire I-Location
'' O
' O
– O
Jayavarman B-Person
II I-Person
( O
802–850 O
) O

Moustava B-Organization
Belialov I-Organization
– O
( O
Perak B-Organization
FA I-Organization
) O

Mark B-Person
Bell I-Person
— O
did O
not O
finish O
( O
→ O
no O
ranking O
) O

Downs B-Person
, I-Person
Thomas I-Person
Nelson I-Person

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
Orchidaceae I-Organization
genera I-Organization

University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Arkansas I-Organization

Major B-Organization
General I-Organization
Andrew B-Person
Stewart I-Person
( O
2004–2006 O
) O

Brent B-Organization
Cross I-Organization
tube I-Organization
station I-Organization

Netherlands B-Organization
national I-Organization
rugby I-Organization
union I-Organization
team I-Organization

Ayer B-Organization
Fue I-Organization
Kumbia I-Organization
Kings I-Organization
, I-Organization
Hoy I-Organization
Es I-Organization
Kumbia I-Organization
All I-Organization
Starz I-Organization
'' O
( O
2006 O
) O

' O
'' O
14 O
Porsche B-Organization
'' O
' O
'' O

San B-Location
Pedro I-Location
de I-Location
Atacama I-Location

Gerard B-Person
Salonga I-Person
- O
June O
28 O
, O
2008 O
- O
July O
26 O
, O
2008 O
; O
August O
16 O
, O
2008 O
- O
August O
23 O
, O
2008 O

He O
is O
a O
Certified B-Organization
Public I-Organization
Accountant I-Organization
. O

Ícaro B-Person
Passos I-Person
de I-Person
Oliveira I-Person

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Gers I-Location
department I-Location

The O
marriage O
was O
dissolved O
in O
1956 O
and O
his O
ex-wife O
then O
married O
Sir B-Person
Nigel I-Person
Fisher I-Person
MP I-Person
in O
1956 O
. O

Guerrero B-Location
, I-Location
Coahuila I-Location

Hon. B-Person
Sir I-Person
John I-Person
Hubert I-Person
Ward I-Person
( O
20 O
March O
1870 O
– O
2 O
December O
1938 O
) O

Lac B-Location
de I-Location
Paladru I-Location
( O
G O
) O

Paul B-Person
Millsap I-Person
( O
19 O
) O

Jodhpur B-Organization
National I-Organization
University I-Organization

a O
threat O
to O
destroy O
or O
damage O
property O
may O
also O
amount O
to O
an O
offence O
under O
section O
2 O
of O
the O
Criminal B-Organization
Damage I-Organization
Act I-Organization
1971 I-Organization
. O

Victoria B-Person
Azarenka I-Person
( O
4 O
) O

' O
'' O
George B-Person
Lauder I-Person
'' O
' O

' O
'' O
Colin B-Person
Kazim-Richards I-Person
'' O
' O

Halle B-Organization
( I-Organization
Westf I-Organization
) I-Organization
station I-Organization

** O
Deep B-Location
transverse I-Location
perineal I-Location
muscle I-Location

Rufus B-Organization
Does I-Organization
Judy I-Organization
at I-Organization
Carnegie I-Organization
Hall I-Organization
'' O

A193]] O
at O
Hartley B-Location
, I-Location
Northumberland I-Location

Assistant B-Organization
Secretary I-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Navy I-Organization
( I-Organization
Manpower I-Organization
and I-Organization
Reserve I-Organization
Affairs I-Organization
) I-Organization

St B-Location
George I-Location
's I-Location
Oval I-Location
, O
Port B-Location
Elizabeth I-Location

`` O
Do B-Organization
n't I-Organization
Let I-Organization
the I-Organization
Sun I-Organization
Go I-Organization
Down I-Organization
on I-Organization
Me I-Organization
'' O

Philippine B-Location
Sea I-Location
Frontier I-Location

Since O
then O
he O
has O
lived O
in O
Cheshire B-Location
, O
13 O
miles O
from O
Crewe B-Location
, O
with O
his O
wife O
and O
three O
children O
( O
including O
a O
son O
born O
February O
2004 O
and O
a O
daughter O
born O
November O
2005 O
) O
. O

Collin B-Person
Peterson I-Person
( O
D-MN O
) O

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
highways I-Organization
in I-Organization
New I-Organization
South I-Organization
Wales I-Organization

'' O
Synanthedon B-Location
tipuliformis I-Location
'' O
( O
Clerck O
, O
1759 O
) O

'' O
Süper B-Organization
Lig I-Organization
: O
' O
'' O

Defected O
to O
the O
People B-Location
's I-Location
Republic I-Location
of I-Location
China I-Location

' O
'' O
Damián B-Person
Rodríguez I-Person
'' O
' O
– O
Uruguay B-Location

85137 O
: O
Kenny B-Person
Burrell I-Person
- O
''Generation O
'' O

Terry B-Person
Board I-Person
( I-Person
footballer I-Person
born I-Person
1968 I-Person
) I-Person

1979 O
– O
Steve B-Person
Hillage I-Person
– O
''Open O
'' O

Antigonus B-Person
II I-Person
Mattathias I-Person

He O
was O
buried O
on O
17 O
November O
at O
Stone-next-Dartford B-Organization
. O

The O
competition O
was O
held O
in O
Colorado B-Location
Springs I-Location
, O
USA B-Location
from O
February O
7 O
to O
12 O
, O
2012 O
. O

Premier B-Organization
of I-Organization
Tasmania I-Organization
— O
Francis B-Person
Smith I-Person

President B-Organization
's I-Organization
Commission I-Organization
on I-Organization
Organized I-Organization
Crime I-Organization

Roll B-Location
's I-Location
partridge I-Location

Air B-Organization
chief I-Organization
marshal I-Organization

It O
is O
located O
in O
the O
Eagles B-Location
Nest I-Location
Wilderness I-Location
, O
Summit B-Location
County I-Location
. O

Google B-Organization
Modular I-Organization
Data I-Organization
Center I-Organization

From O
2008 O
to O
2011 O
, O
he O
was O
the O
U.S. B-Person
Ambassador I-Person
to I-Person
Bangladesh I-Person
. O

'' O
'Name O
'' O
' O
– O
Iberostar B-Organization
Stadium I-Organization

Taşlıyük B-Location
, I-Location
Vezirköprü I-Location

Leach B-Location
's I-Location
storm I-Location
petrel I-Location
, O
''Oceanodroma O
leucorhoa O
'' O

' O
'' O
St. B-Organization
John I-Organization
's I-Organization
Eve I-Organization
'' O
' O
( O
Late O
June O
) O

Douglas B-Person
Rain I-Person
, O
''Master O
Builder O
'' O

Mystery B-Organization
Science I-Organization
Theater I-Organization
3000 I-Organization
'' O

`` O
Waiting B-Organization
For I-Organization
a I-Organization
Star I-Organization
to I-Organization
Fall I-Organization
'' O

Chester B-Organization
Northgate I-Organization
railway I-Organization
station I-Organization

'' O
Euryphura B-Location
concordia I-Location
'' O
( O
Hopffer O
, O
1855 O
) O

`` O
Somebody B-Organization
Help I-Organization
Me I-Organization
'' O
( O
Jackie B-Person
Edwards I-Person
) O

Mausoleum B-Organization
of I-Organization
Galla I-Organization
Placidia I-Organization
in O
Ravenna B-Location
, O
Italy B-Location

Nossa B-Location
Senhora I-Location
das I-Location
Dores I-Location
, I-Location
Sergipe I-Location

' O
'' O
Stirling B-Person
Moss I-Person
'' O
' O

' O
'' O
London B-Location
'' O
' O
, O
United B-Location
Kingdom I-Location
– O
''2009 O
'' O

Ronald B-Location
Dregan I-Location
: I-Location
Dreganomics I-Location

'' O
Red B-Organization
Dwarf I-Organization
'' O

It O
is O
part O
of O
East B-Location
Parish I-Location
. O

Bezerra B-Person
da I-Person
Silva I-Person

Tokyo B-Organization
Xtreme I-Organization
Racer I-Organization
Drift I-Organization
'' O

Juventud B-Organization
Unida I-Organization
de I-Organization
San I-Organization
Miguel I-Organization

The O
lands O
were O
given O
to O
Henry B-Person
Cromwell I-Person
. O

John B-Person
Chapman I-Person
( I-Person
bishop I-Person
) I-Person

OneTouch B-Organization
Premier I-Organization
League I-Organization
: O
''To O
be O
determined O
'' O

United B-Location
States I-Location
Minor I-Location
Outlying I-Location
Islands I-Location

The O
keynote O
was O
by O
Steve B-Person
Wozniak I-Person
. O

** O
Seattle B-Organization
Seahawks I-Organization
34 O
, O
San B-Organization
Francisco I-Organization
49ers I-Organization
13 O

' O
'' O
Jack B-Person
Laugher I-Person
'' O
' O

Nicolás B-Person
Almagro I-Person
( O
shoulder O
injury O
) O

65-0248 O
) O
is O
on O
display O
at O
the O
Museum B-Organization
of I-Organization
Aviation I-Organization
at O
Robins B-Organization
Air I-Organization
Force I-Organization
Base I-Organization
in O
Houston B-Location
County I-Location
, O
Georgia B-Location

2012-2013 O
- O
Dulce B-Organization
Amor I-Organization

David B-Person
Diaz I-Person
vs. I-Person
Manny I-Person
Pacquiao I-Person

`` O
Kelly B-Person
Clarkson I-Person
co-wrote O
this O
track O
from O
the O
album O
. O

Louisiana B-Organization
Highway I-Organization
66 I-Organization

' O
'' O
Aprilia B-Organization
'' O
' O

Les B-Organization
Mots I-Organization
( I-Organization
album I-Organization
) I-Organization

VVD B-Organization
( O
2 O
seats O
) O

In O
August O
1914 O
he O
together O
with O
his O
brother O
Olģerts O
traveled O
through O
Spain B-Location
. O

Potamogeton B-Location
× I-Location
angustifolius I-Location

Sakurabashi B-Organization
Station I-Organization
( I-Organization
Shizuoka I-Organization
) I-Organization

Langrenus B-Location
( I-Location
crater I-Location
) I-Location

`` O
Jar B-Organization
of I-Organization
Hearts I-Organization
'' O

Monmouth B-Location
, I-Location
Illinois I-Location
– O
$ O
15,839 O

Taye B-Person
Diggs I-Person
as O
Sam B-Person
Bennett I-Person

Al B-Location
Tahoe I-Location
, I-Location
California I-Location

It O
is O
the O
site O
name O
for O
the O
Saqqaq B-Organization
culture I-Organization
. O

It O
is O
found O
in O
Mexico B-Location
, O
Guatemala B-Location
, O
Costa B-Location
Rica I-Location
, O
Panama B-Location
, O
Colombia B-Location
, O
Venezuela B-Location
and O
Brazil B-Location
. O

** O
Principality B-Organization
of I-Organization
Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen I-Organization
– O
Joseph B-Person
Friedrich I-Person
( O
1715–1769 O
) O

Socialist B-Organization
Party I-Organization
of I-Organization
California I-Organization

Count B-Person
Ludwig I-Person
von I-Person
Cobenzl I-Person

Lincoln B-Location
, I-Location
Nebraska I-Location

*2007 O
: O
Science B-Organization
& I-Organization
Nature I-Organization
'' O

Planned B-Organization
Parenthood I-Organization
Federation I-Organization
of I-Organization
America I-Organization
, I-Organization
Inc I-Organization
. I-Organization

Bacardi B-Organization
family I-Organization
, O
owners O
of O
Bacardi B-Organization
Rums I-Organization
, O
Grey B-Organization
Goose I-Organization
, O
Martini B-Organization
& I-Organization
Rossi I-Organization
and O
Dewar B-Organization
's I-Organization

Asymphorodes B-Location
mediostriatus I-Location
'' O
J.F.G O
. O

File O
: O
Zlatorudne O
mlyny.jpg|Mills O
in O
Zlaté B-Location
Hory I-Location

Pedro B-Person
Girón I-Person
Acuña I-Person
Pacheco I-Person
( O
1445–1466 O
) O

Prominent O
students O
included O
William B-Person
James I-Person
Mayo I-Person
and O
Charles B-Person
Horace I-Person
Mayo I-Person
. O

Yamatotakeru B-Organization
no I-Organization
mikoto I-Organization
was O
the O
son O
of O
Emperor B-Organization
Keiko I-Organization
. O

In O
1846 O
, O
James B-Person
Hardiman I-Person
stated O
: O

Gigi B-Person
Fernández I-Person
Etsuko B-Person
Inoue I-Person
Kumiko B-Person
Okamoto I-Person
Neige B-Person
Dias I-Person

New B-Organization
York I-Organization
State I-Organization
Route I-Organization
78 I-Organization

He O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Lok B-Organization
Sabha I-Organization
from O
1957 O
to O
1967 O
and O
again O
from O
1971 O
to O
1972 O
. O

All O
the O
organisers O
' O
profits O
are O
donated O
to O
a O
charity B-Organization
, O
Birdlife B-Organization
International I-Organization
. O

' O
'' O
Khorezm B-Location
'' O
' O

Renny B-Person
Quow I-Person
, O
Kevon B-Person
Pierre I-Person
, O
Jamil B-Person
James I-Person
, O
Damion B-Person
Barry I-Person

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Vendée I-Location
department I-Location

' O
'' O
Singapore B-Organization
Slammers I-Organization
'' O
' O

Richard B-Person
Jefferson I-Person
( O
26 O
) O

Sault B-Location
Ste. I-Location
Marie I-Location
, I-Location
Ontario I-Location

' O
'' O
Henry B-Person
Callaway I-Person
'' O
' O

Parupalli B-Person
Kashyap I-Person
' O
'' O
3–0 O

Nahom B-Person
Mesfin I-Person
Tariku I-Person

2Held O
only O
by O
the O
Chief B-Person
of I-Person
the I-Person
Army I-Person
Staff I-Person

Yvonne B-Person
Strahovski I-Person
– O
Chuck B-Organization
'' O

'' O
Archonias B-Location
brassolis I-Location
'' O
( O
Fabricius O
, O
1777 O
) O

Image O
: O
FrankKnox O
c1943 O
g399009.jpg|Publisher O
' O
'' O
Frank B-Person
Knox I-Person
'' O
' O
from O
Illinois B-Location

'' O
Campeonato B-Organization
Maranhense I-Organization
: O
32 O
'' O
' O

She O
is O
the O
ex-wife O
of O
Stephen B-Person
Hawking I-Person
. O

| O
style= O
'' O
text-align O
: O
left O
; O
'' O
George B-Person
Connelly I-Person

In O
2006 O
the O
band O
recorded O
a O
performance O
for O
The B-Organization
Henry I-Organization
Rollins I-Organization
Show I-Organization
. O

He O
lives O
in O
Austin B-Location
, I-Location
Texas I-Location
. O

rect O
165 O
166 O
230 O
180 O
Monte B-Location
Nuovo I-Location

Kid B-Person
Rock I-Person
and O
Sheryl B-Person
Crow I-Person

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
Hot I-Organization
100 I-Organization
number-one I-Organization
singles I-Organization
of I-Organization
1992 I-Organization
( I-Organization
U.S I-Organization
. I-Organization
) I-Organization

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Loire I-Location
department I-Location

Durgapur B-Location
( O
private O
vehicles O
) O

Thanks B-Organization
for I-Organization
the I-Organization
Feedback I-Organization
'' O
( O
2014 O
) O

Simi B-Location
Valley I-Location
, I-Location
California I-Location

In O
September O
2011 O
, O
he O
signed O
a O
one-year O
contract O
with O
PAOK B-Organization
in O
Greece B-Location
. O

The B-Organization
Lladró I-Organization
Museum I-Organization

Paul B-Person
Ritchie I-Person
( I-Person
footballer I-Person
, I-Person
born I-Person
1975 I-Person
) I-Person

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
New I-Organization
Hampshire I-Organization
rivers I-Organization

''65 O
Damien B-Person
Woody I-Person
G O
( O
IR O
) O
7px O

Some O
of O
its O
elements O
, O
such O
as O
certain O
choices O
in O
its O
ordering O
, O
reflect O
features O
particular O
to O
the O
Tang B-Location
dynasty I-Location
, O
but O
no O
conclusive O
proof O
of O
an O
actual O
date O
of O
composition O
has O
yet O
been O
found O
. O

Jaipur B-Location
, I-Location
Adilabad I-Location
district I-Location

This O
is O
often O
not O
the O
case O
( O
see O
conformity B-Organization
) O
. O

State-owned B-Organization
( O
9.7 O
% O
) O

He O
joined O
Newton B-Organization
Heath I-Organization
in O
February O
1899 O
as O
a O
replacement O
for O
James B-Person
McNaught I-Person
. O

Herman B-Organization
E. I-Organization
Talmadge I-Organization
( O
D O
) O

Diocese B-Location
of I-Location
Argyll I-Location
and I-Location
The I-Location
Isles I-Location
( I-Location
Episcopal I-Location
) I-Location

Wayne B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
West I-Location
Virginia I-Location

Ted B-Person
Musgrave I-Person
drove O
the O
renumbered O
No O
. O

of O
the O
Archaeological B-Organization
Journal I-Organization
'' O
. O

'' O
Inspiration O
'' O
( O
Wide B-Organization
Hive I-Organization
Records I-Organization
, O
2004 O
) O

Leonards B-Location
Pond I-Location
( I-Location
Rochester I-Location
, I-Location
Massachusetts I-Location
) I-Location

Silakhor-e B-Location
Sharqi I-Location
Rural I-Location
District I-Location

He O
published O
his O
first O
book O
of O
poems O
at O
his O
own O
expense O
in O
Glasgow B-Location
in O
1836 O
. O

' O
'' O
Second O
: O
' O
'' O
Kaho B-Person
Onodera I-Person

Seven B-Organization
Network I-Organization
( O
6 O
) O

`` O
U.S. B-Organization
Department I-Organization
of I-Organization
Justice I-Organization
. O

91205 O
in O
Glendale B-Location
• O
41,431 O

The O
Mission]] O
'' O
' O
'' O
Robert B-Person
Bolt I-Person

Arun B-Person
Govil I-Person
, O
Tanuja B-Person
, O
Amjad B-Person
Khan I-Person

Punjab B-Location
, I-Location
India I-Location

***** O
Charles B-Person
III I-Person
, I-Person
King I-Person
of I-Person
Spain I-Person
( O
1716-1788 O
) O

Aqeel B-Person
Abbas I-Person
Jafari I-Person

Ladorudz B-Location
, I-Location
Koło I-Location
County I-Location

Birdman B-Person
- O
Priceless B-Organization
'' O
==== O

'' O
Stargate B-Organization
SG-1 I-Organization
'' O

Takashi B-Person
Ukaji I-Person
as O
Akira B-Person
Kurosawa I-Person

São B-Location
Francisco I-Location
de I-Location
Assis I-Location

Vinod B-Person
Khanna I-Person
, O
Shabana B-Person
Azmi I-Person

: O
Archibald B-Person
Acheson I-Person
, I-Person
4th I-Person
Earl I-Person
of I-Person
Gosford I-Person

Edward B-Person
Royle I-Person
, O
1980 O
. O

Sharrukin B-Organization
II I-Organization
( O
Sargon B-Person
II I-Person
) O

Development B-Organization
Education I-Organization
Society I-Organization

19 O
, O
from O
Manchester B-Location
, I-Location
UK I-Location
/ O
now O
NSW B-Location

** O
Duke B-Person
of I-Person
Loulé I-Person
( O
1869–1870 O
) O

Before O
1945 O
the O
area O
was O
part O
of O
Germany B-Location
. O

C. B-Person
E. I-Person
Webber I-Person

Observatorio B-Organization
de I-Organization
La I-Organization
Cañada I-Organization

: O
:1st O
Round O
7 O
( O
Hafjell B-Organization
, O
Norway B-Location
) O

Miloslav B-Person
HamrRudolf I-Person
KarlecekVaclav O
Bohumil B-Person
Váňa I-Person

Marvel B-Organization
Cinematic I-Organization
Universe I-Organization
tie-in I-Organization
comics I-Organization

Sunnyvale B-Location
( O
140,081 O
) O

''November O
20 O
, O
1977 O
at O
the O
Pontiac B-Organization
Silverdome I-Organization
, O
Pontiac B-Location
, I-Location
Michigan I-Location
'' O

Channing B-Person
Frye I-Person
, O
Marcin B-Person
Gortat I-Person
( O
10 O
) O

Johnnie B-Person
To I-Person
, O
Law B-Person
Wing-cheung I-Person

**Monarch O
– O
Kingdom B-Location
of I-Location
Lunda I-Location
( O
1687–1709 O
) O

20px O
' O
'' O
South B-Location
Sulawesi I-Location
'' O
' O

Médaille B-Organization
commémorative I-Organization
de I-Organization
la I-Organization
guerre I-Organization
1914-1918 I-Organization

Jørgen B-Person
Hammergaard I-Person
Hansen I-Person

Anthony B-Person
Quinn I-Person
, O
William B-Person
Conrad I-Person

'' O
Belenois B-Location
aurota I-Location
'' O
( O
Fabricius O
, O
1793 O
) O

Velika B-Location
Plana I-Location
- O
16,210 O

Maha B-Organization
Sarakham I-Organization
University I-Organization
, O
Thailand B-Location

Billdal B-Location
( O
part O
of O
) O

Marabou B-Location
stork I-Location
, O
''Leptoptilos O
crumeniferus O
'' O

''Oberst O
'' O
Kurt B-Person
Freiherr I-Person
von I-Person
Liebenstein I-Person
, O
21 O
December O
1942 O
– O
1 O
January O
1943 O
( O
acting O
leader O
) O

Yamanaka B-Organization
Castle I-Organization
, O
Mishima B-Location
, I-Location
Shizuoka I-Location

*1379 O
– O
Charles B-Person
Roberts I-Person
– O
2007 O

Super B-Organization
League I-Organization
Greece I-Organization
: O
1982–83 B-Organization

Vanessa B-Person
Kraven I-Person
defeated O
She B-Person
Nay I-Person
Nay I-Person

*Honorary O
degree O
, O
University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Chicago I-Organization
, O
2008 O

'' O
Mieczysław B-Person
Kotlarczyk I-Person
'' O

'' O
Desire B-Organization
( I-Organization
TV I-Organization
series I-Organization
) I-Organization
'' O
' O

Warren B-Location
Township I-Location
, I-Location
Washington I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location

Berthold B-Person
II I-Person
, I-Person
Duke I-Person
of I-Person
Swabia I-Person

' O
'' O
Files O
Crossroad O
'' O
' O
is O
an O
unincorporated B-Organization
community I-Organization
in O
Berkeley B-Location
County I-Location
, O
West B-Location
Virginia I-Location
. O

' O
'' O
Jim B-Person
Bunning I-Person
'' O
' O
( O
8–8 O
) O

Washington B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Rhode I-Location
Island I-Location

She O
graduated O
from O
Sichuan B-Organization
Normal I-Organization
University I-Organization
, O
where O
she O
majored O
in O
performance O
. O

La B-Location
Unión I-Location
, I-Location
El I-Location
Salvador I-Location

Law B-Organization
& I-Organization
Order I-Organization
: I-Organization
Criminal I-Organization
Intent I-Organization
'' O

' O
'' O
Kärpät B-Organization
'' O
' O
- O
Jokerit B-Organization
4:2 O
( O
3:2 O
, O
3:2 O
, O
2:5 O
, O
2:1 O
, O
1:2 O
, O
2:1 O
) O

He O
died O
in O
Boston B-Organization
, I-Organization
Massachusetts I-Organization
, O
on O
December O
4 O
, O
1891 O
. O

Putties B-Organization
( O
a.k.a O
. O

Kavita B-Person
Krishnamurthy I-Person
, O
Ila B-Person
Arun I-Person

'' O
'Label O
: O
' O
'' O
Mushroom B-Organization
Group I-Organization

Chris B-Person
Paul I-Person
( O
21 O
) O

' O
'' O
Kingdom B-Location
of I-Location
Great I-Location
Britain I-Location
'' O
' O
– O

In O
Husayn B-Person
Bayqarah I-Person
maintains O
control O
of O
Greater B-Location
Khorasan I-Location
. O

Amber B-Person
Lee I-Person
Ettinger I-Person

Doom B-Person
Patrol I-Person
'' O
90-97 O

Neil B-Organization
Bonnett I-Organization
– O
2995 O

Sperm B-Organization
'' O
( O
1994 O
) O

The O
following O
things O
have O
been O
named O
after O
Mikalojus B-Person
Konstantinas I-Person
Čiurlionis I-Person
: O

Aracaju B-Location
, O
Sergipe B-Location
, O
Brazil B-Location

*01 O
/ O
06 O
/ O
91 O
Sinéad B-Person
O'Connor I-Person

Zalkeh B-Location
, I-Location
Sarvabad I-Location

George B-Person
Taylor I-Person
( O
1716-1781 O
) O

Kokuryō-shuku O
( O
国領宿 O
) O
( O
Chōfu B-Location
) O

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
NHL I-Organization
players I-Organization
with I-Organization
2000 I-Organization
career I-Organization
penalty I-Organization
minutes I-Organization

Michael B-Person
K. I-Person
Williams I-Person
as O
Omar B-Person
Little I-Person

1990 B-Location
Currie I-Location
Cup I-Location
Division I-Location
A I-Location

The O
creator-god O
Brahma B-Person
: O
four O

) O
'' O
and O
Cee-Lo B-Person
Green I-Person
. O

Henry B-Person
Adams I-Person
Bellows I-Person
translation O
: O

Helene B-Person
Hayman I-Person
, I-Person
Baroness I-Person
Hayman I-Person

Walter B-Person
von I-Person
Eberhardt I-Person

' O
'' O
Ohio B-Location
'' O
' O

Paracoryza B-Location
'' O
Basilewsky O
, O
1952 O

: O
Dorland B-Organization
's I-Organization
Medical I-Organization
Dictionary I-Organization
( O
1938 O
) O

It O
is O
generally O
found O
in O
the O
QuickTime B-Person
container B-Organization
with O
the O
FourCC B-Person
'rle O
' O
. O

Image O
: O
Painted_wolf.jpg| O
'' O
Lycaon B-Location
pictus I-Location
'' O

Antiochia B-Location
in I-Location
Sittacene I-Location
– O
Antiochus B-Person
I I-Person
Soter I-Person

`` O
Un B-Organization
bel I-Organization
di I-Organization
vedremo I-Organization
'' O
( O
from O
Madame B-Organization
Butterfly I-Organization
) O
by O
Giacomo B-Person
Puccini I-Person

Tim B-Person
Duncan I-Person
– O
1998 O
, O
2004 O
, O
2006 O
, O
2009 O
, O
2010 O
, O
2013 O
, O
2015 O

Reserve B-Organization
Bank I-Organization
of I-Organization
Malawi I-Organization

Vlado B-Person
Papić I-Person
( O
as O
player O
: O
Hajduk B-Organization
Split I-Organization
1986–1988 O
/ O
Dinamo B-Organization
Zagreb I-Organization
1988–1989 O
) O

Genie B-Person
( I-Person
feral I-Person
child I-Person
) I-Person

Little B-Person
Raven I-Person
( I-Person
Arapaho I-Person
leader I-Person
) I-Person

' O
'' O
Gisselberg O
'' O
' O
is O
a O
Stadtteil B-Organization
of O
Marburg B-Location
in O
Hesse B-Location
. O

Franklin B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Arkansas I-Location

The O
album O
's O
lead O
single O
, O
`` O
This B-Organization
is I-Organization
the I-Organization
Time I-Organization
( I-Organization
Ballast I-Organization
) I-Organization
'' O
was O
released O
on O
March O
11 O
, O
2014 O
. O

C. B-Person
L. I-Person
Dellums I-Person

Lyon B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Nevada I-Location

Also O
, O
Jim B-Person
Miller I-Person
came O
in O
with O
only O
three O
weeks O
notice O
as O
a O
late O
replacement O
for O
Frankie B-Person
Edgar I-Person
against O
Matt B-Person
Wiman I-Person
. O

'' O
Glaucocharis B-Location
penetrata I-Location
'' O
( O
Meyrick O
, O
1933 O
) O

' O
'' O
Related B-Organization
'' O
' O

Abbey B-Location
of I-Location
Our I-Location
Lady I-Location
of I-Location
Gethsemani I-Location

Seth B-Person
Hastings I-Person
( O
F O
) O

La B-Location
Vernaz I-Location
( O
74295 O
) O

: O
:E. O
Princess B-Person
Maria I-Person
of I-Person
Greece I-Person
and I-Person
Denmark I-Person
( O
1876–1940 O
) O
, O
married O
Grand B-Person
Duke I-Person
George I-Person
Mikhaelovich I-Person
of I-Person
Russia I-Person
, O
had O
2 O
daughters O
; O
married O
Perikles B-Person
Ioannidis I-Person
, O
no O
issue O

Tiên B-Location
Du I-Location
District I-Location

'' O
Zelleria B-Location
hepariella I-Location
'' O
Stainton O
, O
1849 O

Buckley B-Location
's I-Location
forest I-Location
falcon I-Location

It O
is O
developed O
by O
Turn B-Organization
10 I-Organization
Studios I-Organization
and O
published O
by O
Microsoft B-Organization
Studios I-Organization
. O

`` O
Purity B-Organization
'' O
– O
5:12 O

In O
April O
2014 O
, O
a O
Hindi B-Location
version O
of O
the O
book O
titled O
''Bharat O
Vikhandan O
'' O
was O
released O
. O

Champ-de-Mars B-Organization
( I-Organization
Montreal I-Organization
Metro I-Organization
) I-Organization

University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Buenos I-Organization
Aires I-Organization
, O
2001 O

Clement B-Person
of I-Person
Alexandria I-Person
, O
''Stromata O
'' O
1.131.6 O
. O

It O
was O
described O
by O
Walker B-Person
in O
1859 O
. O

' O
'' O
Prakash B-Person
Amritraj I-Person
'' O
' O
' O
'' O
Rajeev B-Person
Ram I-Person
'' O
' O

According O
to O
Bernard B-Person
Lewis I-Person
: O

Borg B-Organization
El I-Organization
Arab I-Organization
Stadium I-Organization
, O
Alexandria B-Location
, O
Egypt B-Location

Ronald B-Person
J. I-Person
Garan I-Person
, I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person
Michael B-Person
E. I-Person
Fossum I-Person

Arthur B-Person
Lowe I-Person
as O
Captain B-Person
Mainwaring I-Person

McCormick B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
South I-Location
Carolina I-Location
- O
northeast O

' O
'' O
Dominic B-Person
Matteo I-Person
'' O
' O

** O
'' O
South B-Location
Carolina I-Location
'' O
' O

Mr. B-Organization
Lee I-Organization
( I-Organization
restaurant I-Organization
) I-Organization

''Top B-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
World I-Organization
'' I-Organization
( I-Organization
Lynn I-Organization
Anderson I-Organization
album I-Organization
) I-Organization
, O
1973 O

International B-Organization
Rescue I-Organization
( I-Organization
disambiguation I-Organization
) I-Organization

St B-Location
Helena I-Location
Island I-Location
National I-Location
Park I-Location

'' O
Euxoa B-Location
ochrogaster I-Location
'' O
( O
Guenee O
, O
1852 O
) O

Farmton B-Location
, I-Location
Florida I-Location

Perry B-Location
Township I-Location
, I-Location
Coshocton I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location

He O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
National B-Organization
Coordination I-Organization
Committee I-Organization
for I-Organization
Democratic I-Organization
Change I-Organization
. O

Henry B-Organization
Drummond I-Organization
( I-Organization
disambiguation I-Organization
) I-Organization

David B-Person
Rikl I-Person
Jim B-Person
Courier I-Person
Goran B-Person
Ivanišević I-Person
Thomas B-Person
Muster I-Person

'' O
Lordship B-Organization
( I-Organization
seigneurie I-Organization
) I-Organization
of I-Organization
Albret I-Organization
'' O
' O
– O
Amanieu B-Organization
III I-Organization
( O
1100–1130 O
) O

D'Alembert B-Organization
's I-Organization
formula I-Organization

Later O
editions O
were O
edited O
by O
Tom B-Person
Moldvay I-Person
, O
Dave B-Person
Cook I-Person
, O
and O
Frank B-Person
Mentzer I-Person
. O

He O
started O
with O
Tadamon B-Organization
Sour I-Organization
and O
spent O
eight O
years O
. O

' O
'' O
Giancarlo B-Person
Fisichella I-Person
'' O
' O

Gareth B-Person
Edwards I-Person
( I-Person
producer I-Person
) I-Person

'' O
Cuba B-Location
'' O
' O

It O
is O
found O
from O
Estonia B-Location
to O
the O
Pyrenees B-Location
and O
Italy B-Location
and O
from O
France B-Location
to O
Poland B-Location
and O
Slovakia B-Location
. O

'' O
Episyron B-Location
rufipes I-Location
'' O

Westwood B-Location
Highlands I-Location
, I-Location
San I-Location
Francisco I-Location

Gila B-Person
Almagor I-Person
, O
Yehuda B-Person
Barkan I-Person

Roman B-Location
Catholic I-Location
Diocese I-Location
of I-Location
Mandeville I-Location

Original O
from O
Watertown B-Location
, I-Location
Massachusetts I-Location

Saint-Vincent-de-Paul B-Location
, I-Location
Quebec I-Location

Shlomo B-Person
Aviner I-Person
( O
1943- O
) O

' O
'' O
Sarah B-Person
Palin I-Person
'' O
' O

Air B-Organization
Enthusiast I-Organization
'' O
, O
No O
. O

Delta B-Organization
Sigma I-Organization
Epsilon I-Organization

Francis B-Person
Henry I-Person
Taylor I-Person

Diocese B-Location
of I-Location
Cachoeiro I-Location
de I-Location
Itapemirim I-Location

; O
: O
Iraqi B-Organization
Air I-Organization
Force I-Organization

William B-Person
J. I-Person
Hughes I-Person

Stephan B-Person
Eberharter I-Person
( O
2 O
) O

Gymnastics B-Organization
at I-Organization
the I-Organization
2004 I-Organization
Summer I-Organization
Olympics I-Organization
– I-Organization
Women I-Organization
's I-Organization
rhythmic I-Organization
group I-Organization
all-around I-Organization

Jack B-Person
Coggins I-Person
, O
1914–2006 O

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
King I-Organization
Priam I-Organization
's I-Organization
children I-Organization

Tuya B-Person
( I-Person
queen I-Person
) I-Person

' O
'' O
Matthew B-Person
Francis I-Person
'' O
' O
is O
a O
poet O
. O

Dan B-Person
Green I-Person
( I-Person
artist I-Person
) I-Person

Hara B-Organization
Arena I-Organization
, O
Dayton B-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location
, O
United B-Location
States I-Location

For O
higher O
studies O
, O
one O
has O
to O
go O
to O
Narasapuram B-Location
. O

' O
'' O
Gönyeli B-Location
'' O
' O

Tokushima B-Location
, I-Location
Tokushima B-Location

More O
recently O
, O
there O
was O
interest O
in O
the O
supposed O
Face B-Organization
on I-Organization
Mars I-Organization
. O

The B-Organization
Adventures I-Organization
of I-Organization
Brisco I-Organization
County I-Organization
, I-Organization
Jr I-Organization
. I-Organization
'' O

Joe B-Person
Perry I-Person
( O
June O
6 O
, O
1992 O
) O

Junior B-Organization
Woodchucks I-Organization
( O
also O
under O
name O
`` O
Huey B-Organization
, I-Organization
Dewey I-Organization
and I-Organization
Louie I-Organization
'' O
) O

Sir B-Person
Louis I-Person
Mallet I-Person
( O
1823–1890 O
) O

Rod B-Person
Carew I-Person
was O
named O
the O
American B-Organization
League I-Organization
Rookie I-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Year I-Organization
. O

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Guadeloupe I-Location
department I-Location

Narendra B-Person
Patel I-Person
, I-Person
Baron I-Person
Patel I-Person

Nicolas B-Person
Girard I-Person
, O
Parti B-Organization
Québécois I-Organization

'' O
Kingdom B-Organization
of I-Organization
Denmark I-Organization
'' O
' O
– O
Eric B-Person
V I-Person
( O
1259–1286 O
) O

Montclar B-Organization
( I-Organization
disambiguation I-Organization
) I-Organization

** O
' O
'' O
Flanders B-Location
'' O
' O
- O
Luc B-Person
Van I-Person
den I-Person
Brande I-Person
( O
1992-1999 O
) O

The B-Location
Grove I-Location
, O
Thornley B-Location
, O
Thringarth B-Location
, O
Toft B-Location
Hill I-Location
, O
Townfield B-Location
, O

W. B-Person
Graham I-Person
Claytor I-Person
, I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person

Emperor B-Person
Xian I-Person
of I-Person
Han I-Person
( O
189–220 O
) O
( O
31 O
) O

Pepłowo B-Location
, I-Location
Mława I-Location
County I-Location

Taliabu B-Location
masked I-Location
owl I-Location

James B-Person
, I-Person
son I-Person
of I-Person
Alphaeus I-Person

*1991 O
: O
Ingrid B-Person
Chavez I-Person
: O
''May O
19 O
, O
1992 O
'' O

Estadio B-Organization
El I-Organization
Teniente I-Organization
, O
Rancagua B-Location
, O
Chile B-Location

*Member O
, O
International B-Organization
Bar I-Organization
Association I-Organization

Lewis B-Person
David I-Person
de I-Person
Schweinitz I-Person

Fox B-Organization
Sports I-Organization
News I-Organization
Asia I-Organization
( O
replaced O
ESPNews B-Organization
Asia I-Organization
) O

Budweiser B-Organization
Budvar I-Organization
Brewery I-Organization

George B-Person
Ide I-Person
Butler I-Person

The O
Hong B-Organization
Kong I-Organization
Inland I-Organization
Revenue I-Organization
Department I-Organization
has O
issued O
guidance O
relating O
to O
its O
interpretation O
of O
the O
case O
. O

West B-Location
Ukrainian I-Location
People I-Location
's I-Location
Republic I-Location

Order B-Organization
, I-Organization
Lawfulness I-Organization
, I-Organization
Justice I-Organization

Sir B-Person
Thomas I-Person
Wolryche I-Person
, I-Person
1st I-Person
Baronet I-Person

1996 O
: O
''Wildwechsel O
'' O
with O
Fettes B-Organization
Brot I-Organization

Centre B-Organization
for I-Organization
Fine I-Organization
Arts I-Organization
, I-Organization
Brussels I-Organization

Jane B-Person
Bown I-Person
- O
Lifetime O
Achievement O

Seminary B-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Immaculate I-Organization
Conception I-Organization

He O
died O
on O
August O
25 O
, O
1992 O
in O
Boca B-Location
Raton I-Location
, I-Location
Florida I-Location
. O

In O
the O
15th O
century O
it O
was O
a O
personal O
property O
of O
the O
Odrowąż B-Organization
clan I-Organization
. O

' O
'' O
Marc B-Person
López I-Person
Rafael B-Person
Nadal I-Person

Sir B-Person
William I-Person
Airmine I-Person
, I-Person
2nd I-Person
Baronet I-Person
( O
1622–1658 O
) O

' O
'' O
Plovdiv B-Location
'' O
' O
, O
Bulgaria B-Location
( O
since O
2004 O
) O

`` O
New B-Organization
York I-Organization
Times I-Organization
Book I-Organization
Review I-Organization
'' O
28 O
October O
1984 O

Isaac B-Person
ben I-Person
Moses I-Person
Arama I-Person
. O

Japan B-Location
's O
population O
began O
decreasing O
in O
2005 O
. O

Lists B-Organization
of I-Organization
people I-Organization
from I-Organization
the I-Organization
Dominican I-Organization
Republic I-Organization

He O
sent O
his O
future O
counterpart O
back O
in O
his O
place O
( O
Episode O
: O
`` O
Visionary B-Organization
'' O
) O
. O

Pierson B-Location
, I-Location
Illinois I-Location

Maximilien B-Person
de I-Person
Béthune I-Person
, I-Person
Duke I-Person
of I-Person
Sully I-Person

Bad B-Organization
Education I-Organization
( I-Organization
TV I-Organization
series I-Organization
) I-Organization

He O
died O
in O
Cologne B-Location
. O

Aneta B-Person
Kowalska I-Person
/ O
Artur B-Person
Szeliski I-Person

Jor B-Organization
Bagh I-Organization
metro I-Organization
station I-Organization

Sheikh B-Person
Mansur I-Person
was O
based O
here O
in O
1786 O
. O

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
constituencies I-Organization
of I-Organization
Andhra I-Organization
Pradesh I-Organization
Vidhan I-Organization
Sabha I-Organization

' O
'' O
Tug B-Person
McGraw I-Person
'' O
' O
( O
5 O
) O

Attorney-General B-Person
– O
' O
'' O
Ralph B-Person
Hanan I-Person
'' O
' O
. O

Winchendon B-Location
( I-Location
CDP I-Location
) I-Location
, I-Location
Massachusetts I-Location

Swansea B-Organization
Metropolitan I-Organization
University I-Organization

: O
' O
'' O
1959 O
'' O
' O
: O
John B-Person
Aldridge I-Person

Mount B-Organization
Pisgah I-Organization
, I-Organization
Iowa I-Organization

Elders B-Person
, I-Person
Joycelyn I-Person
( O
born O
1933 O
) O
, O
former O
Surgeon B-Person
General I-Person
of I-Person
the I-Person
United I-Person
States I-Person

García B-Person
Íñiguez I-Person
of I-Person
Pamplona I-Person

He O
worked O
as O
a O
lawyer O
in O
Turku B-Location
from O
1892-1916 O
. O

Helena B-Person
Kennedy I-Person
, I-Person
Baroness I-Person
Kennedy I-Person
of I-Person
The I-Person
Shaws I-Person

Huaca B-Location
del I-Location
Sol I-Location

He O
attended O
Amherst B-Organization
College I-Organization
. O

''Glider B-Organization
'' I-Organization
( I-Organization
The I-Organization
Sight I-Organization
Below I-Organization
album I-Organization
) I-Organization

Boundary B-Location
Ranges I-Location
, O
just O
S O
of O
Iskut B-Location
River I-Location

Ray B-Person
Jarvis I-Person
( I-Person
American I-Person
football I-Person
) I-Person

Galba B-Person
' O
'' O
D O
'' O
' O
' O
'' O
L O
'' O
' O
and O
Otho B-Person
' O
'' O
D O
'' O
' O
' O
'' O
L O
'' O
' O

'' O
Pilodeudorix B-Location
catalla I-Location
'' O
( O
Karsch O
, O
1895 O
) O

Channel B-Location
Islands I-Location
of I-Location
California I-Location
, O

Bedford B-Organization
and I-Organization
Cambridge I-Organization
Railway I-Organization
, O
1865 O

Teenage B-Organization
Mutant I-Organization
Ninja I-Organization
Turtles I-Organization
( I-Organization
1987 I-Organization
TV I-Organization
series I-Organization
) I-Organization

Jonathan B-Person
Pryce I-Person
as O
Lytton B-Person
Strachey I-Person

Governorate B-Location
General I-Location
of I-Location
Brazil I-Location
( O
1549-1572 O
/ O
1578-1607 O
/ O
1613-1621 O
) O

Marika B-Person
Zanforlin I-Person
/ O
Federico B-Person
Degli I-Person
Esposti I-Person

Tara B-Location
( I-Location
mountain I-Location
) I-Location

Brian B-Person
Morgan I-Person
– O
production O

Mullica B-Location
Hill I-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
Jersey I-Location

2006–07 B-Location
Real I-Location
Madrid I-Location
C.F. I-Location
season I-Location

Canadian B-Organization
Council I-Organization
of I-Organization
Chief I-Organization
Executives I-Organization

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Somme I-Location
department I-Location

' O
'' O
' O
'' O
( O
France B-Location
) O
'' O

: O
** O
27 O
- O
Berane B-Location
, O
Rožaje B-Location
, O
Plav B-Location
, O
Andrijevica B-Location

Moustafa B-Person
Soheim I-Person
, O
Farid B-Person
El-Ashmawi I-Person
, O
Ahmed B-Person
El-Hamy I-Person
El-Husseini I-Person
, O
Mohamed B-Person
Gamil I-Person
El-Kalyoubi I-Person
, O
Sameh B-Person
Abdel I-Person
Rahman I-Person

Nort-Leulinghem B-Location
( O
62622 O
) O

' O
'' O
1317 B-Organization
in I-Organization
art I-Organization
'' O
' O

Coconut B-Location
Creek I-Location
, I-Location
Florida I-Location
, O
United B-Location
States I-Location

Frank B-Organization
E. I-Organization
Doremus I-Organization
( O
D O
) O

Rajiv B-Location
Gandhi I-Location
International I-Location
Cricket I-Location
Stadium I-Location

`` O
Violins B-Organization
and I-Organization
Tambourines I-Organization
'' O

Mammoth B-Location
Cave I-Location
National I-Location
Park I-Location

Kamianets-Podilskyi B-Location
in O
Ukraine B-Location
'' O
( O
since O
1993 O
) O
'' O

Faridpur]] O
, O
and O
part O
of O
Noakhali B-Location
District I-Location
. O

`` O
Danza B-Organization
Kuduro I-Organization
'' O
- O
Don B-Person
Omar I-Person
feat O
. O

Bandō B-Person
Kakitsu I-Person
I I-Person

Desiderio B-Person
Scaglia I-Person
( O
9 O
February O
1626 O
– O
6 O
October O
1627 O
) O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Canadian B-Organization
House I-Organization
of I-Organization
Commons I-Organization
in O
1872 B-Organization
for O
Lunenburg B-Location
. O

Rivière B-Location
des I-Location
Créoles I-Location

Human B-Organization
Rights I-Organization
Commission I-Organization
of I-Organization
Malaysia I-Organization

Mariah B-Person
Carey I-Person
– O
Daydream B-Organization
'' O

; O
IGN B-Organization
's I-Organization
Best I-Organization
of I-Organization
2013 I-Organization
Awards I-Organization

' O
'' O
Herbert B-Person
Covington I-Person
Bonner I-Person
( O
D O
) O
92.5 O
% O
' O
'' O
W O
. O

Chananel B-Person
ben I-Person
Chushiel I-Person

Straight B-Person
Clark I-Person
'' O
( O
Third O
round O
) O
'' O

Cape B-Location
May I-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
Jersey I-Location

It O
is O
located O
within O
the O
Bergamo B-Location
Alps I-Location
. O

'' O
Killer B-Organization
'' O
– O
Adamski B-Person
feat O
. O

' O
'' O
Aaron B-Person
Fultz I-Person
'' O
' O
( O
3–0 O
) O

The B-Organization
13th I-Organization
Floor I-Organization
Elevators I-Organization

Kenny B-Person
Irwin I-Person
, I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person

Coverage O
of O
the O
1987 B-Organization
stock I-Organization
market I-Organization
crash I-Organization

Miranda B-Person
Cosgrove I-Person
( O
1993- O
) O

Robert B-Person
Mercer I-Person
was O
Bishop B-Organization
of I-Organization
Matabeleland I-Organization
in O
Zimbabwe B-Location
from O
1977 O
to O
1989 O
. O

John B-Person
Chambers I-Person
( O
1922-2001 O
) O

Hipólito B-Person
Yrigoyen I-Person
resigned O
as O
President B-Organization
of I-Organization
Argentina I-Organization
following O
a O
week O
of O
violent O
antigovernment O
demonstrations O
. O

''Live B-Organization
at I-Organization
the I-Organization
Copa I-Organization
'' I-Organization
( I-Organization
The I-Organization
Temptations I-Organization
album I-Organization
) I-Organization
, O
1968 O

2006 O
: O
The B-Organization
Coast I-Organization
Is I-Organization
Clear I-Organization
'' O

Rajesh B-Person
Krishnan I-Person
, O
K. B-Organization
S. I-Organization
Chitra I-Organization

The O
elevation O
is O
3944 O
feet O
( O
1202 O
m O
) O
above B-Organization
sea I-Organization
level I-Organization
. O

It O
covers O
the O
stretch O
between O
Gothenburg B-Location
and O
Karesuando B-Location
via O
Trollhättan B-Location
, O
Vänersborg B-Location
, O
Mellerud B-Location
, O
Åmål B-Location
, O
Säffle B-Location
, O
Grums B-Location
, O
Sunne B-Location
, O
Torsby B-Location
, O
Stöllet B-Location
, O
Malung B-Location
, O
Mora B-Location
, O
Sveg B-Location
, O
Brunflo B-Location
, O
Östersund B-Location
, O
Strömsund B-Location
, O
Dorotea B-Location
, O
Vilhelmina B-Location
, O
Storuman B-Location
, O
Sorsele B-Location
, O
Arvidsjaur B-Location
, O
Jokkmokk B-Location
, O
Gällivare B-Location
, O
Svappavaara B-Location
, O
and O
Vittangi B-Location
. O

Cisówek B-Location
, I-Location
Suwałki I-Location
County I-Location

' O
'' O
Lindsay B-Person
Davenport I-Person
'' O
' O
/ O
' O
'' O
Natasha B-Person
Zvereva I-Person
'' O
' O
defeated O
Larisa B-Person
Neiland I-Person
/ O
Elena B-Person
Tatarkova I-Person
6–4 O
, O
6–4 O

Ingram B-Organization
Hill I-Organization
( O
active O
; O
unsigned O
) O

16 O
' O
'' O
Len B-Person
Dawson I-Person
'' O
' O

Francis B-Person
J. I-Person
Myers I-Person
( O
D O
) O

Ángel B-Person
Custodio I-Person
Quintana I-Person

Elizabeth B-Organization
City I-Organization
, I-Organization
NC I-Organization

** O
Vietnam B-Organization
during I-Organization
the I-Organization
Second I-Organization
World I-Organization
War I-Organization

Prince B-Person
Clemens I-Person
Wenceslaus I-Person
of I-Person
Saxony I-Person
1768–1803 O

533 B-Organization
: O
Personal B-Organization
Communications I-Organization
Services I-Organization

Pearl B-Location
River I-Location
, I-Location
Mississippi I-Location

Midland B-Organization
and I-Organization
Great I-Organization
Northern I-Organization
Joint I-Organization
Railway I-Organization
183¼ O
miles O
( O
298 O
km O
) O

Audi B-Organization
Sport I-Organization
Audi B-Organization
Quattro I-Organization
A1 I-Organization

** O
Atwater B-Organization
Library I-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Mechanics I-Organization
' I-Organization
Institute I-Organization
of I-Organization
Montreal I-Organization

Michał B-Person
Krasenkow I-Person
( O
born O
1963 O
) O

Jack B-Person
Morris I-Person
, O
April O
7 O
, O
1984 O

It O
runs O
from O
a O
connection O
with O
the O
Death B-Organization
Valley I-Organization
Fault I-Organization
Zone I-Organization
in O
the O
Amargosa B-Location
Valley I-Location
northward O
to O
a O
termination O
in O
the O
Fish B-Location
Lake I-Location
Valley I-Location
. O

'' O
Dahlica B-Location
lazuri I-Location
'' O
( O
Clerck O
, O
1759 O
) O

*The O
Bennington B-Organization
Battle I-Organization
Monument I-Organization
in O
Bennington B-Location
, I-Location
Vermont I-Location
, O
1889 O
. O

: O
: O
: O
: O
: O
''B. B-Location
'' I-Location
var. I-Location
''collina I-Location
'' I-Location

: O
' O
'' O
Tony B-Person
O'Donohue I-Person
'' O
' O
( O
incumbent O
) O
- O
5,617 O

History B-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Los I-Organization
Angeles I-Organization
Rams I-Organization

Label O
: O
Hallmark B-Organization
Entertainment I-Organization

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
New I-Organization
Testament I-Organization
minuscules I-Organization

Interview O
with O
Granta B-Organization
( O
October O
5 O
, O
2013 O
) O

UFC B-Organization
on I-Organization
FX I-Organization
: I-Organization
Johnson I-Organization
vs. I-Organization
McCall I-Organization

George B-Person
Pachymeres I-Person
( O
1242–1310 O
) O

South B-Location
Dakota I-Location
( O
2014 O
) O

Bishop B-Organization
Ludden I-Organization
Junior I-Organization
/ I-Organization
Senior I-Organization
High I-Organization
School I-Organization
is O
named O
after O
him O
. O

It O
is O
situated O
on O
the O
reach O
above O
Hurley B-Organization
Lock I-Organization
. O

Father B-Organization
Murphy I-Organization
'' O
( O
1981–1983 O
) O

*1982 O
: O
TED B-Organization
Ankara I-Organization
Kolejliler I-Organization
, O
Oyak B-Organization
Renault I-Organization

Givira B-Location
hypomelaleuca I-Location
'' O
Zukowsky O
, O
1954 O

Wesley B-Person
D. I-Person
Sweetser I-Person
( O
1919–2006 O
) O
, O
critic O

There O
are O
currently O
76 O
vehicles O
available O
to O
members O
, O
with O
the O
majority O
of O
them O
located O
in O
Kitchener-Waterloo B-Organization
. O

Cedar B-Location
Mill I-Location
, I-Location
Oregon I-Location

She O
regularly O
contributes O
to O
National B-Organization
Geographic I-Organization
, O
Sports B-Organization
Illustrated I-Organization
, O
Newsweek B-Organization
, O
Time B-Organization
, O
Latina B-Organization
, O
and O
Texas B-Organization
Monthly I-Organization
. O

It O
is O
now O
simply O
called O
Prison B-Organization
Officer I-Organization
. O

Antônio B-Person
Rodrigo I-Person
Nogueira I-Person

*October O
3 O
– O
Jake B-Person
Eisenhart I-Person

Quirinus B-Person
of I-Person
Tegernsee I-Person

He O
was O
part O
of O
the O
Argentina B-Location
men I-Location
's I-Location
national I-Location
volleyball I-Location
team I-Location
. O

Floral B-Location
Park I-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
York I-Location

Mount B-Organization
Gambier I-Organization
Prison I-Organization
, O
the O
privately O
run O
facility O
, O
built O
in O
the O
1990s O
. O

97 O
Mark B-Person
Wheeler I-Person
DT O

Robert B-Person
T. I-Person
A. I-Person
Innes I-Person

Dona B-Person
Drake I-Person
as O
Mihirmah O

'' O
Bedellia B-Location
somnulentella I-Location
'' O
( O
Zeller O
, O
1847 O
) O

Spring B-Location
Grove I-Location
Township I-Location
, I-Location
Houston I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Minnesota I-Location

Errol B-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
Hampshire I-Location

*96.1 O
MHz O
Zinc96 B-Organization
– O
Active B-Person
rock I-Person
- O
Grant B-Organization
Broadcasters I-Organization

four O
segments O
, O
all O
written O
by O
Tonino B-Person
Guerra I-Person

Roman B-Location
Catholic I-Location
Archdiocese I-Location
of I-Location
Chicago I-Location

Leśniki B-Location
, I-Location
Lubusz I-Location
Voivodeship I-Location

Mary B-Person
Ellen I-Person
Pleasant I-Person

( O
see O
Fecal B-Organization
transplant I-Organization
) O
. O

The O
20th O
century O
plans O
for O
a O
Pechora-Kama B-Organization
Canal I-Organization
came O
to O
nought O
as O
well O
. O

' O
'' O
Gu B-Person
Jiaming I-Person
'' O
' O

Twickenham B-Organization
Stadium I-Organization
, O
London B-Location
, O
England B-Location

'' O
Witney B-Organization
and I-Organization
District I-Organization
League I-Organization
'' O
' O
: O

In O
1912 O
, O
the O
family O
moved O
to O
Montreal B-Location
. O

Finta B-Location
, I-Location
Dâmbovița I-Location

Stockbridge B-Location
, I-Location
Michigan I-Location
– O
$ O
17,614 O

Howard B-Person
R. I-Person
Lamar I-Person

Roman B-Location
Catholic I-Location
Archdiocese I-Location
of I-Location
Anqing I-Location

'' O
Trachydora B-Location
thyrsophora I-Location
'' O
Meyrick O
, O
1897 O

Silesian B-Organization
People I-Organization
's I-Organization
Party I-Organization

1992 B-Organization
Major I-Organization
League I-Organization
Baseball I-Organization
expansion I-Organization
draft I-Organization

I B-Organization
Belong I-Organization
to I-Organization
You I-Organization
/ I-Organization
How I-Organization
Many I-Organization
Ways I-Organization

'' O
Opostegoides B-Location
scioterma I-Location
'' O
( O
Meyrick O
, O
1920 O
) O

Ghost B-Organization
in I-Organization
the I-Organization
Shell I-Organization
: I-Organization
Stand I-Organization
Alone I-Organization
Complex I-Organization
'' O

Tarbes B-Organization
Pyrénées I-Organization
Rugby I-Organization

He O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
influential O
JASON B-Organization
Defense I-Organization
Advisory I-Organization
Group I-Organization
. O

'' O
Laval B-Location
'' O
' O

Kalbar B-Location
, I-Location
Queensland I-Location

Discovered O
in O
1852 O
at O
Cermiky O
, O
also O
known O
as O
Tschermig O
in O
Bohemia B-Location
. O

Wednesbury B-Location
is O
the O
first O
area O
supplied O

See O
also O
: O
List B-Organization
of I-Organization
towers I-Organization

Lake B-Location
Pleasant I-Location
( I-Location
Washington I-Location
) I-Location

Hertford B-Organization
County I-Organization
High I-Organization
School I-Organization
, O
Ahoskie B-Location

He O
was O
elected O
member O
of O
the O
National B-Organization
Assembly I-Organization
of I-Organization
Slovenia I-Organization
in O
1992 O
. O

Te B-Location
Henga I-Location
( I-Location
Bethells I-Location
Beach I-Location
) I-Location

'' O
Parornix B-Location
szocsi I-Location
'' O
Gozmany O
, O
1952 O

Janaki]] O
, O
S. B-Person
P. I-Person
Balasubrahmanyam I-Person

Heppner B-Organization
Junior I-Organization
/ I-Organization
Senior I-Organization
High I-Organization
School I-Organization

Cicely B-Person
Courtneidge I-Person
, O
Ernest B-Person
Truex I-Person

`` B-Organization
Tempted I-Organization
'' I-Organization
( I-Organization
Squeeze I-Organization
song I-Organization
) I-Organization
, O
song O
by O
Squeeze B-Organization
and O
covered O
by O
other O
artists O
1981 O

** O
Ros B-Organization
na I-Organization
Rún I-Organization
'' O

Mission B-Organization
Blue I-Organization
'' O
( O
2014 O
) O

Holt B-Location
, I-Location
Alabama I-Location

Nick B-Person
Stevens I-Person
( O
2014 O
) O

Another O
well-known O
individual O
, O
Geoffrey B-Person
of I-Person
Monmouth I-Person
, O
served O
as O
Lord B-Location
Bishop I-Location
of I-Location
St I-Location
Asaph I-Location
from O
1152 O
to O
1155 O
. O

Al B-Organization
Jazira I-Organization
Mohammed I-Organization
Bin I-Organization
Zayed I-Organization
Stadium I-Organization

Chicago B-Organization
Bulls I-Organization
( O
6 O
) O

He O
is O
said O
to O
paint O
in O
the O
style O
of O
Palma B-Person
il I-Person
Giovane I-Person
. O

Mountain B-Location
Communities I-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Tejon I-Location
Pass I-Location

*49-1095 O
- O
Selfridge B-Organization
Military I-Organization
Air I-Organization
Museum I-Organization
, O
Selfridge B-Organization
ANGB I-Organization
, O
Mount B-Location
Clemens I-Location
, I-Location
Michigan I-Location
. O

Published O
: O
Warsaw B-Location
, O
1851 O

'' O
New B-Organization
Japan I-Organization
Pro I-Organization
Wrestling I-Organization
'' O
' O

Frans B-Person
Banninck I-Person
Cocq I-Person

Oleksandr B-Person
Babiy I-Person
– O
FC B-Organization
Zenit I-Organization
St. I-Organization
Petersburg I-Organization
– O
1998–1999 O

Chauvé B-Location
( O
44038 O
) O

Afan B-Organization
Lido I-Organization
were O
promoted O
to O
the O
Welsh B-Organization
Premier I-Organization
League I-Organization
. O

**71 O
- O
Frangista B-Organization
, O
Viniani B-Location

These O
vehicles O
would O
be O
able O
to O
place O
into O
a O
LEO B-Location
or O
into O
GTO B-Location
. O

Jöns B-Person
Jacob I-Person
Berzelius I-Person

Crash]] O
'' O
( O
1973 O
) O
, O
J. B-Person
G. I-Person
Ballard I-Person

Both O
sides O
of O
his O
family O
were O
originally O
from O
Eastern B-Location
Europe I-Location
, O
including O
Poland B-Location
. O

' O
'' O
Benigno B-Person
Aquino I-Person
III I-Person
'' O
' O

The B-Organization
Daily I-Organization
News I-Organization
'' O

''Colleen O
'' O
was O
transferred O
to O
the O
Irish B-Location
Free I-Location
State I-Location
on O
19 O
February O
1923 O
and O
broken O
up O
in O
1950 O
. O

Premier B-Person
( I-Person
Canada I-Person
) I-Person

Ian B-Person
Ferguson I-Person
( I-Person
footballer I-Person
, I-Person
born I-Person
1967 I-Person
) I-Person

Nurullah B-Person
Sağlam I-Person
( O
2009 O
) O

Centerville B-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location

New B-Location
Mexico I-Location
( O
2014 O
) O

Tim B-Organization
& I-Organization
Eric I-Organization

It O
was O
created O
in O
1869 O
for O
the O
banker O
George B-Person
Glyn I-Person
. O

Angola B-Organization
women I-Organization
's I-Organization
national I-Organization
under-16 I-Organization
and I-Organization
under-17 I-Organization
basketball I-Organization
team I-Organization

William B-Person
Powers I-Person
, I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person

Castries B-Location
, O
79.5 O
km² O

Patrick B-Person
O'Donnell I-Person
, O
Catholic B-Location
Bishop I-Location
of I-Location
Raphoe I-Location
, O
Most O
Rev O
. O

`` B-Organization
Rewind I-Organization
'' I-Organization
( I-Organization
Devlin I-Organization
song I-Organization
) I-Organization
, O
2013 O

'' O
Charaxes B-Location
cithaeron I-Location
'' O

Żakowo B-Location
, I-Location
Greater I-Location
Poland I-Location
Voivodeship I-Location

'' O
Bactra B-Location
lancealana I-Location
'' O
( O
Hübner O
, O
1799 O
) O

*Municipal O
Human B-Organization
Development I-Organization
Index I-Organization
: O
.650 O
( O
2000 O
) O

Muhammad B-Person
ibn I-Person
Abd I-Person
al-Wahhab I-Person
( O
1703–1792 O
) O

It O
is O
based O
at O
Herston B-Location
, O
Swanage B-Location
, O
Dorset B-Location
. O

'' O
Runaround B-Organization
Sue I-Organization
'' O
( O
Dion B-Person
DiMucci I-Person
, O
Ernie B-Person
Maresca I-Person
) O

' O
'' O
Joe B-Person
DiMaggio I-Person
'' O
' O
'' O

'' O
Finkenstein B-Location
am I-Location
Faaker I-Location
See I-Location
'' O
( O
Slov B-Organization
. I-Organization
: O
''Bekštanj O
'' O
) O
( O
' O
'' O
3 O
'' O
' O
) O

' O
'' O
Senegal B-Location
'' O
' O

Harcharan B-Person
Chawla I-Person
( O
1926–2001 O
) O
, O
writer O

CMLL B-Organization
Super I-Organization
Viernes I-Organization
( I-Organization
May I-Organization
2010 I-Organization
) I-Organization

' O
'' O
Triple B-Person
H I-Person
'' O
' O
'' O

Route B-Organization
159 I-Organization
( I-Organization
Connecticut I-Organization
– I-Organization
Massachusetts I-Organization
) I-Organization

Rocko B-Person
- O
''Wordplay O
'' O
=== O

Autaugaville B-Location
, I-Location
Alabama I-Location

Thunder B-Organization
Agents I-Organization
'' O
6-7 O
( O
2012 O
) O

Kunio B-Person
Maekawa I-Person
, O
architect O

Raymond B-Person
Felton I-Person
( O
7 O
) O

It O
is O
found O
in O
China B-Location
. O

Paul B-Person
Cole I-Person
( O
GB O
) O

Stoke B-Organization
Bridge I-Organization
, I-Organization
Ipswich I-Organization

Something B-Organization
Bitchin I-Organization
' I-Organization
This I-Organization
Way I-Organization
Comes I-Organization
'' O
( O
1989 O
) O

'' O
Tragopogon B-Location
pratensis I-Location
'' O
- O
introduced O

The O
top O
three O
placings O
were O
later O
acknowledged O
in O
publications O
including O
the O
Football B-Organization
Record I-Organization
'' O
and O
are O
considered O
official O
. O

P. B-Person
N. I-Person
Okeke-Ojiudu I-Person

' O
'' O
Emmanuel B-Person
Philibert I-Person
, I-Person
Duke I-Person
of I-Person
Savoy I-Person
'' O
' O
and O
his O
children O
( O
son O
of O
Beatrice B-Person
of I-Person
Portugal I-Person
, I-Person
Duchess I-Person
of I-Person
Savoy I-Person
, O
daughter O
of O
Manuel B-Person
I I-Person
) O

The B-Location
Dangling I-Location
Man I-Location
'' O
( O
1985 O
) O

Crunchy B-Person
Black I-Person
( O
1995–2006 O
, O
2013-present O
) O

Military B-Organization
Assistance I-Organization
Command I-Organization
, I-Organization
Vietnam I-Organization
– I-Organization
Studies I-Organization
and I-Organization
Observations I-Organization
Group I-Organization

DJ B-Person
Quik I-Person
- O
Primary O
Artist O

Nouvelle B-Organization
Revue I-Organization
Française I-Organization

'' O
Normiflo B-Organization
'' O
' O

`` O
Too B-Organization
Young I-Organization
'' O
( O
Nat B-Person
King I-Person
Cole I-Person
) O

''UFOs O
— O
Identified O
'' O
, O
1968 O
, O
Random B-Organization
House I-Organization
, O
ISBN O
0-394-45003-5 O

Gerald B-Person
Henry I-Person
Rendall I-Person

Xavier B-Person
Malisse I-Person
6–2 O
, O
6–2 O
, O
2–0 O
retired O

Hanapepe B-Location
, I-Location
Hawaii I-Location

SV B-Organization
Centro I-Organization
Social I-Organization
Deportivo I-Organization
Barber I-Organization

'' O
Kingdom B-Location
of I-Location
Hungary I-Location
'' O
' O
– O
Andrew B-Person
II I-Person
( O
1205–1235 O
) O

Henry B-Person
Nielsen I-Person
- O
Gøgler O

Pinehurst B-Location
, I-Location
Montgomery I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Texas I-Location

When O
she O
was O
23 O
, O
she O
adopted O
Mark B-Person
Anthony I-Person
McDermott I-Person
, O
her O
husband O
's O
then O
16-year-old O
son O
from O
his O
first O
marriage O
. O

The B-Organization
Avengers I-Organization
'' O
“Who’s O
Who O
? O
? O

It O
is O
found O
in O
Bolivia B-Location
. O

Webb B-Person
Pierce I-Person
( O
1921–1991 O
) O
– O
singer O

' O
'' O
Guernsey B-Location
'' O
' O

It O
is O
known O
from O
north-eastern O
Algeria B-Location
. O

Oz B-Person
( I-Person
TV I-Person
series I-Person
) I-Person

During O
1979 O
and O
1980 O
, O
he O
taught O
at O
the O
University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Maryland I-Organization
, O
then O
at O
Rhodes B-Organization
College I-Organization
. O

1910–11 B-Organization
Dumbarton I-Organization
F.C. I-Organization
season I-Organization

Garfield B-Location
Township I-Location
, I-Location
Newaygo I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Michigan I-Location

1947–48 B-Organization
Liverpool I-Organization
F.C. I-Organization
season I-Organization

`` O
U B-Organization
Got I-Organization
It I-Organization
Bad I-Organization
'' O

War B-Location
, I-Location
West I-Location
Virginia I-Location

Monster B-Organization
Musume I-Organization
, O
Vol O
. O

Ian B-Person
Hendry I-Person
, O
Alan B-Person
Badel I-Person
, O
Barbara B-Person
Ferris I-Person

Landtag B-Organization
of I-Organization
Brandenburg I-Organization

'' O
Diphymyces B-Location
'' O
I.I.Tav O
. O

Joachim B-Person
Wtewael I-Person
( O
1566–1638 O
) O
, O
1 O
work O

Constitutional B-Organization
Convention I-Organization
( I-Organization
United I-Organization
States I-Organization
) I-Organization

James B-Person
A. I-Person
Burke I-Person
( O
D O
) O

'' O
Stigmella B-Location
ulmiphaga I-Location
'' O
( O
Preissecker O
, O
1942 O
) O

`` O
In B-Organization
For I-Organization
a I-Organization
Penny I-Organization
'' O

Bruce B-Person
Beresford I-Person
( O
Non-Jew O
) O

Salak B-Location
, I-Location
North I-Location
Sumatra I-Location

Vijay B-Location
Pur I-Location
, I-Location
Jammu I-Location
and I-Location
Kashmir I-Location

C B-Organization
& I-Organization
D I-Organization
Canal I-Organization
Museum I-Organization

Apse B-Location
Heath I-Location
, O
Arreton B-Location
) O
. O

** O
'' O
WWE B-Organization
2K16 I-Organization
'' O
- O
Yuke B-Organization
's I-Organization

Harry B-Organization
Carey I-Organization
( I-Organization
disambiguation I-Organization
) I-Organization

Charles B-Person
E. I-Person
Brown I-Person
( I-Person
photographer I-Person
) I-Person

Henry B-Person
IX I-Person
, I-Person
Duke I-Person
of I-Person
Bavaria I-Person
, O
1074–1126 O

'' O
Brownlowia B-Location
'' O
Roxb O
. O

It O
is O
situated O
in O
the O
Huánuco B-Location
Region I-Location
, O
Huamalíes B-Location
Province I-Location
, O
Tantamayo B-Location
District I-Location
. O

Punch B-Location
Bowl I-Location
Falls I-Location

Racing B-Organization
de I-Organization
Olavarría I-Organization

UC B-Organization
Irvine I-Organization
Anteaters I-Organization

List B-Organization
of I-Organization
winners I-Organization
of I-Organization
Sahitya I-Organization
Akademi I-Organization
Awards I-Organization
for I-Organization
writing I-Organization
in I-Organization
Rajasthani I-Organization
language I-Organization

'' O
Having B-Organization
a I-Organization
Party I-Organization
'' O
( O
1982 O
) O

Duchy B-Organization
of I-Organization
Münsterberg I-Organization

A O
Warner B-Organization
Bros I-Organization
. I-Organization
Production O
. O

GSIM B-Location
Yenişehir I-Location
Ice I-Location
Hockey I-Location
Hall I-Location

They O
were O
confirmed O
again O
in O
the O
early O
17th O
century O
by O
King B-Person
Mátyás I-Person
II I-Person
of I-Person
Hungary I-Person
. O

Issue O
69 O
: O
Detective B-Person
Chimp I-Person

`` O
Mike B-Person
Doughty I-Person
of O
Soul B-Organization
Coughing I-Organization

John B-Person
McDonald I-Person
( I-Person
rugby I-Person
league I-Person
) I-Person

' O
'' O
TT B-Organization
Pro I-Organization
League I-Organization
'' O
'8 O
teams O

Jameer B-Person
Nelson I-Person
( O
7 O
) O

He B-Organization
's I-Organization
So I-Organization
Fine I-Organization

Hachiōji B-Location
, I-Location
Tokyo I-Location

Suteh B-Location
, I-Location
Kurdistan I-Location

Royal B-Organization
Shakespeare I-Organization
Theatre I-Organization
, O
Stratford-upon-Avon B-Location
, O
England B-Location
September O
2011 O

Voorlezer B-Organization
's I-Organization
House I-Organization

It O
is O
found O
in O
China B-Location
( O
Hainan B-Location
) O
. O

Ksenia B-Person
Monko I-Person
/ O
Kirill B-Person
Khaliavin I-Person

Reception O
for O
''Starters O
'' O
has O
been O
positive O
, O
with O
the O
Los B-Organization
Angeles I-Organization
Times I-Organization
calling O
it O
`` O
well O
executed O
'' O
. O

Bartholomew B-Location
County I-Location
( O
north-northeast O
) O

E. B-Person
H. I-Person
Shepard I-Person

Siméon B-Person
Denis I-Person
Poisson I-Person

Lifestyles B-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Rich I-Organization
and I-Organization
Famous I-Organization
'' O
, O
July O
1986–September O
1986 O
. O

`` O
Hands B-Organization
Up I-Organization
'' O
- O
3:20 O
( O
Ottawan B-Organization
) O

brevoculus O
'' O
= O
Mesonacis B-Location
bonnensis I-Location
'' O

All B-Organization
Saints I-Organization
Cathedral I-Organization
, I-Organization
Halifax I-Organization

Redshank B-Location
, O
''Tringa O
totanus O
'' O

Evgenia B-Person
Shishkova I-Person
/ O
Vadim B-Person
Naumov I-Person

Bolívar B-Location
State I-Location
, I-Location
Colombia I-Location

RF O
1 O
) O
in O
Dublin B-Location
. O

'' O
Eupithecia B-Location
pauxillaria I-Location
'' O
Boisduval O
, O
1840 O

John B-Person
Shelton I-Person
Lawrence I-Person

Saigyō B-Person
Hōshi I-Person
( O
1118–1190 O
) O

Fabolous B-Person
- O
Loso B-Organization
's I-Organization
Way I-Organization
'' O
'' O
( O
July O
28 O
, O
2009 O
) O
''=== O

X.A.N. B-Organization
Thessaloniki I-Organization
B.C I-Organization
. I-Organization

Despite O
a O
formal O
petition O
that O
was O
filed O
with O
the O
FCC O
against O
the O
proposed O
sale O
, O
the O
sale O
was O
approved O
by O
the O
Federal B-Organization
Trade I-Organization
Commission I-Organization
on O
October O
6 O
, O
2008 O
. O

*MacLaren O
's O
Pub O
— O
How B-Organization
I I-Organization
Met I-Organization
Your I-Organization
Mother I-Organization
'' O
( O
2005 O
) O

The O
sequel O
featured O
Vinay B-Person
Pathak I-Person
reprising O
his O
role O
as O
the O
main O
lead O
. O

'' O
Stigmella B-Location
nylandriella I-Location
'' O
( O
Tengstrom O
, O
1848 O
) O

Glencoe B-Location
, I-Location
KwaZulu-Natal I-Location

SUTD O
's O
permanent O
campus O
opened O
in O
January O
2015 O
at O
Changi B-Location
, O
near O
Changi B-Location
Business I-Location
Park I-Location
. O

Our B-Location
New I-Location
Quarters I-Location

142nd B-Organization
Indiana I-Organization
Infantry I-Organization
Regiment I-Organization

Luther B-Organization
Burbank I-Organization
Center I-Organization
for I-Organization
the I-Organization
Arts I-Organization

The B-Location
Crossings I-Location
, I-Location
Florida I-Location
- O
3.89 O
% O

Ramón B-Person
Ramírez I-Person
( I-Person
Dominican I-Person
pitcher I-Person
) I-Person

`` O
U B-Organization
Ca I-Organization
n't I-Organization
Touch I-Organization
This I-Organization
'' O

Twelfth B-Organization
Air I-Organization
Force I-Organization
, O
12 O
December O
1954 O
– O
10 O
December O
1957 O

Kubrat B-Person
, I-Person
Prince I-Person
of I-Person
Panagyurishte I-Person
. O

Lady B-Person
Gaga I-Person
( O
Feat O
. O

Star B-Organization
Trek I-Organization
: I-Organization
Voyager I-Organization
'' O

James B-Person
Edward I-Person
Smith I-Person

Marion B-Organization
, I-Organization
IN I-Organization
Micropolitan I-Organization
Statistical I-Organization
Area I-Organization

' O
'' O
El B-Organization
secreto I-Organization
de I-Organization
sus I-Organization
ojos I-Organization
'' O
' O
'' O

2000 B-Organization
Men I-Organization
's I-Organization
Olympic I-Organization
Games I-Organization
100m I-Organization
Breaststroke I-Organization
( I-Organization
Sydney I-Organization
) I-Organization

He O
was O
admitted B-Organization
to I-Organization
the I-Organization
bar I-Organization
at O
Hiawatha B-Location
, I-Location
Kansas I-Location
, O
in O
1898 O
. O

Sang B-Organization
Doo I-Organization
! I-Organization
Let I-Organization
's I-Organization
Go I-Organization
to I-Organization
School I-Organization
'' O

' O
'' O
Color B-Person
: O
' O
'' O
Jackie B-Person
Stewart I-Person

Latter B-Organization
Day I-Organization
Church I-Organization
of I-Organization
Christ I-Organization

164 O
Gunnison B-Location
, I-Location
Utah I-Location
$ O
14,537 O

Gwangdeoksan B-Location
( I-Location
Gangwon I-Location
/ I-Location
Gyeonggi I-Location
) I-Location

Finsch B-Location
's I-Location
parakeet I-Location

Sir B-Person
Archibald I-Person
Campbell I-Person
, I-Person
1st I-Person
Baronet I-Person

Brian B-Person
McKnight I-Person
- O
`` O
Still O
'' O

Chung B-Organization
Wan I-Organization
( I-Organization
constituency I-Organization
) I-Organization

West B-Location
Bank I-Location
: O
78,600 O
. O

North B-Location
Frontenac I-Location
, I-Location
Ontario I-Location

Philippine B-Organization
Normal I-Organization
University I-Organization

Sylvester B-Person
, I-Person
David I-Person
. O

Reg B-Person
Baker I-Person
( O
1899– O
? O

Tatem B-Location
Elementary I-Location
School I-Location
, I-Location
Collingswood I-Location
, I-Location
NJ I-Location

Christine B-Person
Truman I-Person
'' O
( O
Semifinalist O
) O
'' O

Guacamayo B-Location
plump I-Location
toad I-Location

La B-Location
Clotte I-Location
( O
17113 O
) O

Juan B-Person
Manuel I-Person
Fangio I-Person

Offices O
are O
in O
Baltimore B-Organization
, I-Organization
Maryland I-Organization
, O
Dallas B-Organization
, I-Organization
Texas I-Organization
, O
Columbus B-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location
, O
and O
Louisville B-Location
, I-Location
Kentucky I-Location

Charles B-Person
Bell I-Person
( O
1935–1995 O
) O
, O
artist O

Christ B-Organization
the I-Organization
King I-Organization
in O
Świebodzin B-Location
, O
Poland B-Location

U. B-Organization
S. I-Organization
Army I-Organization
Museum I-Organization
of I-Organization
Hawaii I-Organization

'' O
Scaeosopha B-Location
mitescens I-Location
'' O
( O
T.P O
. O

E B-Organization
102nd I-Organization
Ave I-Organization
MAX I-Organization
Station I-Organization

Rio B-Location
de I-Location
Janeiro I-Location
, O
Brazil B-Location

**** O
White-winged B-Location
serotine I-Location
''Neoromicia O
tenuipinnis O
'' O
LC O

- O
PLFA O
Polish B-Organization
American I-Organization
Football I-Organization
League I-Organization

Lilley B-Organization
Road–Lower I-Organization
Rouge I-Organization
River I-Organization
Bridge I-Organization

Kazi B-Person
Zulkader I-Person
Siddiqui I-Person
( O
Techcorp O
) O

Dave B-Person
Allen I-Person
( I-Person
comedian I-Person
) I-Person

Vernon B-Person
Ransford I-Person
( O
1927–1928 O
) O

Central B-Organization
Reorganisation I-Organization
Committee I-Organization
, I-Organization
Communist I-Organization
Party I-Organization
of I-Organization
India I-Organization
( I-Organization
Marxist–Leninist I-Organization
) I-Organization

==== O
'' O
Lepadogaster B-Location
'' O
==== O

' O
'' O
Colin B-Person
Ebelthite I-Person
'' O
' O
' O
'' O
Adam B-Person
Feeney I-Person
'' O
'6–4 O
, O
6–7 O
( O
5–7 O
) O
, O
[10–7] O

Araneta B-Organization
Coliseum I-Organization
, O
Quezon B-Location
City I-Location

She O
is O
currently O
a O
professor O
at O
the O
University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Vienna I-Organization
. O

Selvin B-Person
, I-Person
Joel I-Person
. O

' O
'' O
Amanda B-Person
Stott I-Person
'' O
' O

Essendon B-Organization
Football I-Organization
Club I-Organization

' O
'' O
Sven B-Person
Kramer I-Person
'' O
' O

Jeff B-Person
Lindsay I-Person
( I-Person
engineer I-Person
) I-Person

' O
'' O
Nikita B-Person
Koloff I-Person
'' O
' O
'' O

People B-Person
's I-Person
Artist I-Person
of I-Person
the I-Person
USSR I-Person
( O
October O
4 O
, O
1974 O
) O

He O
is O
son O
of O
former O
San B-Organization
Diego I-Organization
Chargers I-Organization
Head O
coach O
Al B-Person
Saunders I-Person
. O

Citrus B-Location
Heights I-Location
, I-Location
California I-Location

'' O
Eresiomera B-Location
jacksoni I-Location
'' O

Penge B-Organization
West I-Organization
railway I-Organization
station I-Organization

The O
nearest O
are O
in O
Le B-Location
Perthus I-Location
. O

François B-Person
Victor I-Person
Le I-Person
Tonnelier I-Person
de I-Person
Breteuil I-Person

Pirate B-Organization
's I-Organization
Lair I-Organization
on I-Organization
Tom I-Organization
Sawyer I-Organization
Island I-Organization

** O
'' O
Duchy B-Organization
of I-Organization
Brabant I-Organization
'' O
' O
– O
Henry B-Person
I I-Person
( O
1190–1235 O
) O

' O
'' O
Thiemo B-Person
de I-Person
Bakker I-Person
'' O
'6–4 O
, O
4–6 O
, O
6–2 O

Woodside B-Location
Park I-Location
( I-Location
Silver I-Location
Spring I-Location
, I-Location
Maryland I-Location
) I-Location

The O
original O
name O
''Vailima O
'' O
was O
used O
by O
Peckham B-Person
& I-Person
Peckham B-Person
, O
1907 O
. O

Doubleday B-Organization
( O
Garden B-Location
City I-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
York I-Location
) O
. O

Crawling B-Organization
Back I-Organization
to I-Organization
You I-Organization
( I-Organization
Daughtry I-Organization
song I-Organization
) I-Organization

Chris B-Person
Kraus I-Person
( I-Person
American I-Person
writer I-Person
) I-Person

Ultimately O
, O
she O
lost O
in O
three O
sets O
to O
Julia B-Person
Görges I-Person
in O
the O
semifinals O
. O

Monroeville B-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location

'' O
Vincent B-Person
Ng I-Person
( O
翁清海 O
) O
' O
'' O

Landaff B-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
Hampshire I-Location

It O
is O
operated O
by O
the O
Northern B-Organization
Railways I-Organization
. O

'' O
December O
4 O
'' O
– O
The B-Person
First I-Person
Hundred I-Person
Years I-Person

' O
'' O
Žatec B-Location
'' O
' O
- O

Mossel B-Location
Bay I-Location
Local I-Location
Municipality I-Location

It O
would O
be O
another O
80 O
years O
however O
, O
before O
Scotland B-Organization
played O
their O
first O
full O
match O
, O
against O
Surrey B-Organization
in O
1865 O
, O
where O
they O
won O
by O
172 O
runs O
. O

Slangin O
' O
ft. O
UGK B-Organization

Uma B-Person
Thurman I-Person
- O
Kill B-Organization
Bill I-Organization
: I-Organization
Volume I-Organization
1 I-Organization
'' O
as O
The B-Person
Bride I-Person
/ I-Person
Beatrix I-Person
Kiddo I-Person

Shahgarh B-Location
, O
seized O
in O
1857 O

Pope B-Person
Celestine I-Person
V I-Person

The O
2005 O
edition O
of O
the O
ceremonies O
paid O
tribute O
to O
the O
victims O
of O
the O
2004 B-Organization
Tsunami I-Organization
. O

'' O
Holy B-Organization
Roman I-Organization
Empire I-Organization
'' O
' O
– O
Frederick B-Person
III I-Person
( O
1452–1493 O
) O

Nicolas B-Person
Prost I-Person
Nick B-Person
Heidfeld I-Person
Mathias B-Person
Beche I-Person

Villard B-Organization
( I-Organization
imprint I-Organization
) I-Organization

Pink B-Organization
World I-Organization
'' O
by O
Planet B-Organization
P I-Organization
Project I-Organization

Boston B-Location
Harbor I-Location
, I-Location
Washington I-Location

Anna B-Location
, I-Location
Ohio I-Location

He O
was O
born O
at O
Clydach B-Location
, O
Glamorgan B-Location
. O

In O
1576 O
, O
he O
became O
Prince-Abbot B-Organization
of O
Stavelot B-Location
. O

Brian B-Person
Lee I-Person
, O
co-founder O
of O
Legalzoom.com B-Organization
, O
ShoeDazzle.com B-Organization
, O
and O
The B-Organization
Honest I-Organization
Company I-Organization

' O
'' O
Michael B-Person
Pedersen I-Person
Friis I-Person
'' O
' O
( O
1857–1944 O
) O

Titsingh B-Person
, I-Person
Isaac I-Person
. I-Person
( O
1834 O
) O
. O

From O
Bayerisch B-Location
Eisenstein I-Location
to O
Poysdorf B-Location

He O
currently O
plays O
for O
Trois-Rivières B-Organization
Caron I-Organization
& I-Organization
Guay I-Organization
of O
the O
Ligue B-Organization
Nord-Américaine I-Organization
de I-Organization
Hockey I-Organization
. O

** O
'' O
Orissa B-Location
'' O
' O
: O
Sambalpur B-Location
, O
Anugul B-Organization
, O
Bargarh B-Location
, O
Balangir B-Location
, O
Debagarh B-Location
, O
Dhenkanal B-Location
, O
Jharsuguda B-Location
and O
Sonapur B-Location

Jeff B-Person
Chandler I-Person
as O
Singer O

He O
was O
a O
problematic O
teenager O
but O
he O
was O
accepted O
to O
the O
University B-Organization
of I-Organization
Oklahoma I-Organization
. O

On O
March O
4 O
, O
1897 O
, O
he O
began O
serving O
in O
the O
United B-Organization
States I-Organization
House I-Organization
of I-Organization
Representatives I-Organization
and O
remained O
until O
his O
death O
in O
Washington B-Location
, I-Location
D.C I-Location
. I-Location
, O
on O
January O
11 O
, O
1903 O
, O
before O
the O
start O
of O
what O
would O
have O
been O
a O
fourth O
term O
. O

Songs B-Organization
in I-Organization
A I-Organization
Minor I-Organization
'' O

' O
'' O
Lornna B-Person
Soto I-Person
'' O
' O

Highland B-Location
, I-Location
Iowa I-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Wisconsin I-Location

'' O
Turkish B-Organization
Cup I-Organization
: O
' O
'' O

Tokushima B-Location
, I-Location
Tokushima B-Location

He O
is O
included O
in O
the O
Syrian B-Person
Martyrology I-Person
of I-Person
Rabban I-Person
Silba I-Person
'' O
. O

San B-Location
Cristóbal I-Location
de I-Location
La I-Location
Laguna I-Location
, I-Location
España I-Location

Peyton B-Person
Manning I-Person
currently O
holds O
the O
record O
with O
5,477 O
passing O
yards O
in O
2013 O
. O

FC B-Organization
Unirea I-Organization
Urziceni I-Organization

Head O
Coach O
: O
Maurits B-Person
Hendriks I-Person

Indonesian B-Organization
National I-Organization
Party I-Organization

' O
'' O
Where O
There O
Is O
Life O
'' O
' O
is O
an O
album O
by O
Luciano B-Person
. O

Malacopterus B-Location
tenellus I-Location
'' O
( O
Fabricius O
, O
1801 O
) O

*133 O
, O
110 O
, O
102 O
Marco B-Person
Fu I-Person

Hailsham B-Organization
Town I-Organization
F.C I-Organization
. I-Organization

Port B-Location
Elizabeth I-Location
, O
South B-Location
Africa I-Location

Dissolution B-Organization
of I-Organization
the I-Organization
Soviet I-Organization
Union I-Organization

`` O
Tender B-Organization
days I-Organization
'' O
( O
by O
Nogizaka46 B-Organization
) O

Barry B-Person
McGee I-Person
( I-Person
TWIST I-Person
) I-Person

Big B-Location
Black I-Location
River I-Location
( I-Location
Saint I-Location
John I-Location
River I-Location
) I-Location

It O
is O
located O
from O
the O
center B-Organization
of I-Organization
Paris I-Organization
. O

Mertrud B-Location
( O
52321 O
) O

57 O
Mike B-Person
Golic I-Person
, I-Person
Jr I-Person
. I-Person
– O
''Senior O
'' O

' O
'' O
First B-Organization
Past I-Organization
the I-Organization
Post I-Organization
'' O
' O

The O
track O
was O
released O
as O
the O
lead O
single O
in O
Japan B-Location
and O
Norway B-Location
and O
was O
the O
second O
single O
from O
the O
album O
that O
was O
released O
in O
Southeast B-Location
Asia I-Location
in O
2005 O
. O

2008–09 B-Organization
PIHA I-Organization
season I-Organization

Holiday B-Location
World I-Location
& I-Location
Splashin I-Location
' I-Location
Safari I-Location

Ermengarde B-Person
of I-Person
Tours I-Person

In O
June O
1891 O
, O
''Schwalbe O
'' O
went O
to O
Mahé B-Location
in O
the O
Seychelles B-Location
to O
rest O
her O
crew O
. O

MLS B-Organization
Supporters I-Organization
' I-Organization
Shield I-Organization
Winner O

Croke B-Organization
Park I-Organization
, O
Dublin B-Location
, O
Republic B-Location
of I-Location
Ireland I-Location

Communes B-Location
of I-Location
the I-Location
Aisne I-Location
department I-Location

Agatha B-Organization
Christie I-Organization
's I-Organization
Marple I-Organization
'' O

Jura B-Organization
( O
CH O
) O
: O
Saint-Ursanne B-Location

'' O
'Night B-Organization
Mother I-Organization
'' O
– O
by O
Marsha B-Person
Norman I-Person

' O
'' O
Perth B-Organization
Thunder I-Organization
'' O
' O

Count B-Person
of I-Person
Penela I-Person

Okauchee B-Location
Lake I-Location
, I-Location
Wisconsin I-Location

American B-Organization
City I-Organization
Business I-Organization
Journals I-Organization

' O
'' O
Jimmy B-Person
Vasser I-Person
'' O
' O

Don B-Organization
Bowman I-Organization
( I-Organization
disambiguation I-Organization
) I-Organization
, O
various O
people O

Port B-Organization
au I-Organization
Prince I-Organization
, O
Haiti B-Location

'' O
Cyperus B-Location
laevigatus I-Location
'' O
L O
. O

Bach B-Person
Double B-Organization
Violin I-Organization
Concerto I-Organization
in I-Organization
D I-Organization
minor I-Organization

Cedar B-Location
Lawn I-Location
Cemetery I-Location
, I-Location
Paterson I-Location
, I-Location
New I-Location
Jersey I-Location

It O
is O
part O
of O
the O
United B-Organization
States I-Organization
Army I-Organization
Training I-Organization
and I-Organization
Doctrine I-Organization
Command I-Organization
and O
is O
the O
site O
of O
the O
U.S. B-Organization
Army I-Organization
War I-Organization
College I-Organization
. O

Mobile B-Location
County I-Location
, I-Location
Alabama I-Location

He O
has O
played O
for O
the O
Japanese B-Organization
national I-Organization
team I-Organization
. O

`` O
Run B-Organization
It I-Organization
! I-Organization
'' O

United B-Organization
Left I-Organization
( I-Organization
Spain I-Organization
) I-Organization

Dirac B-Organization
Medal I-Organization
( O
1996 O
) O

Tommy B-Person
Aaron I-Person
( O
1 O
) O

Underwood B-Location
's I-Location
bonneted I-Location
bat I-Location
